准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
肮脏的汉堡
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
一个风雨交加的黑夜
A dark and stormy night
正是这样的夜晚令我回想起
It's nights like these that remind me of
从前有一刻  蟹老板与海绵宝宝
the time Mr. Krabs and SpongeBob
误以为自己杀了个卫生检查员
thought they killed a health inspector
那是一个晴朗的早晨
It was a bright and sunny morning
蟹堡王
卫生检查员
那味道好像是
That smells like
卫生检查员
the health inspector
快去洗手
Wash your hands
打扫地板
clean the floors
换掉内裤
change your underwear
卫生检查员来了
The health inspector's here
要是他找到一处卫生不合格的地方
If he finds one health violation
就会让我们永远关门大吉
he'll close us down for good
我们必须得尽全力
We've got to do everything in our power
确保他能让蟹堡王合格
to make sure he passes the Krusty Krab
可是蟹老板
But, Mr. Krabs
根本就没什么好怕的
There's no reason to worry
蟹堡王是全宇宙最完美的地方
The Krusty Krab
is the most perfect place in the universe
你是不是根本就没脑子  小子
You really haven't got any brains at all, have you, son?
出去给他需要的东西就行了
Just go out there and give him what he needs
去献殷勤
Pour on the charm
多说好话
Sweet talk him
需要什么吗
What can I get for you
帅哥
handsome?
完蛋了
We're doomed
菜单上的所有东西都给我拿一份
I'm going to need you to bring me
one of everything on the menu
选得好  爱人
Excellent choice, my darling
马上就来
Coming right up
他要所有东西都来一份
He wants one of everything
那咱就给他来份自助大餐
Then we'll give him a smorgasbord
蟹堡王未来的成败在此一举
The future of the Krusty Krab is at stake
尝尝蟹堡王海草热狗吧  先生
Try the Krusty Kelp Dog, sir
黄油藤壶能让你感受天堂的滋味
The Buttered Barnacles are a touch of heaven
浮木粉味美可口
The Powdered Driftwood is exquisite
新鲜淤泥布丁
Fresh Sludge Pudding?
低糖赤潮还要不
More Diet Red Tide?
油炸船只残骸
Some Fried Flotsam?
打住  先生们
Please, gentlemen
我要一个人安安静静完成工作
Leave me to finish my work in peace
这位丰满的检查员用餐可否愉快
And did the voluptuous inspector enjoy his meal?
目前还行
So far, so good
只要再吃一个原味蟹黄堡
I just need to try a plain Krabby Patty
就能完成检查了
and my inspection will be finished
他说只要再来一份蟹黄堡
He says if he gets one more Krabby Patty
就能让我们检查合格了
he'll pass us for the inspection
知道这什么意思吗  亲爱的小子
Do you know what this means, dear boy?
我们过关了
We're in the clear
我们要打断这场康康舞
We interrupt this can-can
插播一则特别简讯
for a special news bulletin
裤头村新闻
请各位注意一名为了吃霸王餐
Be on the lookout for a man
who's been passing himself off
而伪装成卫生检查员的人
as a health inspector in order to obtain free food
以上就是全部内容
That's all for now
霸王餐
Free food?
可能该要跟那位提一提假检查员的事
Maybe we oughta tell our guy about the phony impostor
你个白痴  那位就是假检查员
You loony loofah, he is the impostor
我们上当了
We've been duped
上当了
Duped?
受骗了
Bamboozled
我们上骗了
We've been smeckledorfed
你那根本就不算话
That's not even a word
不过确实
and I agree with ya
看看人家
Look at him
他内裤肯定从来都没换
I bet he never changes his underpants
他肯定咬过鲸鱼吐的泡
I bet he bites whale bubbles
那帽子肯定是他妈给他买的
I bet his mom bought him that hat
如果说那个冒牌货要蟹黄堡的话
If that impostor wants a Krabby Patty
那以海神王的名义  直接成全他
then by Neptune, we'll give him one
火山辣酱
你现在是在与蟹共舞了
You're dancin' with the crab man now
跟我一起干
Join me, boy
不然开除你
or you're fired
这样好像不太对
It doesn't seem right
不过特别的爽
but it feels so good
海马辣根酱
Seahorse radish
海底最呛的东西
the gnarliest stuff in the ocean
等等  我办公室里有罐脚趾甲
Hold on, I've got a jar of toenail clippings in my office
我把它给掉马桶里了
I dropped it in the toilet
那就捞出来  我要拿运动袜来擦干它
Well, fish it out, and I'll dry it with me gym socks
这可是史上最恶心的蟹黄堡了
Why, that's the most diabolical
Krabby Patty ever spawned
我管这叫
I call it
肮脏的汉堡
The Nasty Patty
赶紧把蟹黄堡送上来
Hurry up with that patty
先生给  请慢用
Here you are, sir, enjoy
你好啊  美味
Hello, delicious
快到爸爸这来
Come to papa
快听  他吃掉了
Listen, he ate it
看把人家给噎的
Look at him choke
看人家那疼的
Look at him suffer
看见没  小子
Did you see that, boy?
他脸上那表情
That look on his face
我们打断你们的幸灾乐祸
We interrupt your laughter at other people's expense
插播本则新闻快讯
to bring you this news flash
假检查员已经被捕
The fake inspector has been captured
裤头村新闻
这是他的照片
Here is his picture
如果有个卫生检查员光顾你的餐厅
If a health inspector comes to your restaurant
并且也不是这位
and he's not this guy
就是真的
he's real
这下放心了  对吧蟹老板
That's a relief, eh, Mr. Krabs?
只要把情况解释清楚  他肯定会理解
I'm sure our guy will understand
if we just explain the situation
然后大家就能一笑了之了
Then we can all have a good laugh about it
他多半笑不出来了  小子
I don't think he'll be laughin', boy
怎么了  老板
Why, sir?
因为那汉堡把他给害死了
Because that patty killed him
蟹老板  我们要怎么办
Mr. Krabs, what are we gonna do?
说什么我们
What's this "we" stuff?
肮脏的汉堡是你给他吃的
You fed him the tainted patty
看来你得坐牢去了
Looks like it's the stony lonesome for you
可是是你要我给他吃的
But you told me to give it to him
你本来不是可以阻止我的吗
Well, you could've talked me out of it
说得对  蟹老板
You're right, Mr. Krabs
我有罪
I'm guilty
我在监狱里绝对活不下去
I'll never survive in prison
我会被拿来拖地的
They'll mop up the floor with me
冷静点  小子
Get ahold of yourself, boy
趁没人看见  赶紧处理掉这具尸体
We've got to get rid of this body before anyone sees it
我们得要把他带出去埋了
We've got to take it out and bury it
好恶心  好多细菌
Gross, germs
黏糊糊的  还死气沉沉
It's all icky and corpse-y
这边应该够远了
This should be far enough
现在开始挖
Now, get diggin'
遵命  老板
Yes, sir
在下面磨蹭什么
What's the holdup down there?
有块大石头挡住路了
There's a big rock in the way
那就扔出去继续挖
Well, toss it out and get back to diggin'
遵命  老板
Aye aye, sir
我这是在哪
Where am I?
好像有哪里不对
Somethin' ain't quite right
什么意思啊  蟹老板
What do you mean, Mr. Krabs?
他头还露在外面
His head's stickin' out
抱歉  蟹老板
Sorry, Mr. Krabs
我还以为得帮他透气
I thought he might need some air
去阴间用不着空气
They don't need air where he's going
我们就不该为他说几句悼词吗
Shouldn't we say a few words on his behalf?
他为全世界的卫生检查员带来了荣光
He was a credit to health inspectors everywhere, and
多么勇敢无畏啊
What a brave man
结果却因公殉职了
going in the line of duty like that
为什么
Why?
听好了  你个呆头
Listen here, ya little barnacle
谁都不能
No one
而且谁都不准知道有这回事
and I mean no one can ever know about this
不然你就完了  我就完了
It'll be the end of you, it'll be the end of me
最糟糕的就是
And worst of all
我就完了
It'll be the end of me
都待在那不许动
Stop right where you are
恐怕我们得要逮捕你们两个了
I'm afraid we're going to have to arrest the two of you
蟹老板  我年纪轻轻不能坐牢啊
Mr. Krabs, I'm too young to go to jail
我们犯了什么罪
And what would be the charges?
罪名是你们没有待在蟹堡王
For not being at the Krusty Krab
给我们做几份好吃的蟹黄堡
to whip us up a couple of dee-licious Krabby Patties
笑啊  小子
Laugh, boy
把那泥铲子放后备箱
Put that muddy shovel in the trunk
我们开车送你们回去
and we'll give you a ride back
海绵宝宝  给我听好了
SpongeBob, listen carefully
我们只是要搭便车回蟹堡王去
We're just getting a lift back to the Krusty Krab
你要冷静别慌张  懂不
I need you to stay calm
and don't lose your cool, understand?
现在我能慌张吗
Can I lose my cool now?
怎么说
Why?
把他放后备箱里  小子
Put him in the trunk, boy
我去拖住警察
I'll keep them cops busy
外面是在磨蹭什么
What's the holdup back there?
海神王啊
Oh, Neptune
快起开
Get away
好了
Okay
后面可以了
All set back here
后备箱那个沾满泥的铲子正常得很
Nothing unusual about a muddy shovel in the trunk
可以了
All set
没事吧  小家伙
You okay there, little fella?
他很容易晕车的
He gets carsick real easy
那就系好安全带  我们会稳点开的
Well, buckle up and we'll drive real smooth-like
听好了  海绵宝宝
Now listen, SpongeBob
等我们到了蟹堡王
When we get to the Krusty Krab
我就要你带着
I want you to take
那个铲子
that shovel
把人家拉到什么后门之类的
and bring it around to the back entrance and stuff
我说的是
I mean
放到冰库里
stow it in the freezer
你懂不
Understand?
蟹老板  我懂是懂
I understand, Mr. Krabs
可是你要我怎么处理那个死
but what do you want me to do with the bo
苏打水
ttles of soda
几罐苏打水
Bottles of soda
一回事  都放冰库里
Same thing, put 'em in the freezer
蟹堡王
老天爷啊
Oh, man
真是恶心
This is so gross
后门给锁上了
The back door is locked
我要怎么办才好
What am I gonna do?
你好啊  海绵宝宝
Ahoy there, SpongeBob
你不是还在那外头处理那铲子的吗
I thought you were out back taking care of that shovel
后门给锁上了
Well, the back door was locked
所以我就到这来了
so I came around here
我先失陪一下
So if you'll excuse me
我得去把我帽子放冰库里了
I'm gonna go put my hat in the freezer now
那好吧  海绵宝宝
Okey-dokey, SpongeBob
那小子没事吧
Is that kid okay?
他行为有点诡异
He's actin' a little funny
好笑
Funny?
诡 异
没错
Yeah
他啊  老好笑了
He's a real cut-up, that one
他很会让大伙儿笑口常开
He knows how to keep the crew in stitches
太搞笑了  小子
Good one, boy
他啊  老是戏多
Always on, that one
他那逗趣开关就是关不动
There's no off on his funny switch
行了
Stop it
真是  真是笑死我了
You're, you're killin' me
快看  我差点给忘了
Look, I almost forgot
现在是开收银机撒钱夜
It's Open Cash Register Night
前两名顾客能获得收银机里所有的钱
First two customers
get all the money in the cash register
蟹黄堡先不要了  蟹老板
86 those patties, Krabs
刚接到报警
We just got a call
说是有两个变态在浅坟路埋尸
about two ghouls burying a stiff
over by Shallow Grave Road
我要来杯汽水
I want a soda
汽水给你
Here's your soda
为警官们服务是我一大荣幸
Always a pleasure to serve the folks in blue
那好  再见了
Well, goodbye now
没有加冰
There's no ice
冰
Ice?
你要冰
You want ice?
你真的想要冰吗
Is that what you want, you want ice?
真的要吗
Is that what you want?
你要我做的黑暗勾当已完成  老板
The dark deed you requested is done, sir
我自己去拿
I'll get it myself
冰就在冰库里面  对
Ice is in the freezer, ri?
没有冰
There is no ice
里面从来就没有冰
There's never been any ice
冰都是传说
Ice is just a myth
站一边去
Step aside
你们搞得好像犯了谋杀案一样
You people act like you've committed a murder
好吧
Okay
我全招了
I confess
是海绵宝宝杀的
SpongeBob killed him
什么
What?
你不可以让我背黑锅
You can't pin this whole rap on me
他疯掉了  还失控了
He was insane, out of control
万一你们俩没来  他也会杀掉我的
He would've killed me too if you two hadn't come along
都是蟹老板主谋的
It was all Mr. Krabs' idea
快抓住他  他就一疯狗
Put him down now, he's a mad dog
他睡觉还戴卷发夹
He wears curlers to bed
等等
Wait
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think
你们两个在说什么
What are you two talking about?
我们杀了个卫生检查员
We killed a health inspector
埋了人家  还把他尸体放冰库里
Buried him and then stuffed his body in the freezer
你是说这里面吗
You mean in here?
是空的
It's empty?
这是不是在开什么玩笑
Is this some kind of a joke?
是啊
Yeah
玩笑
A joke
可能他变成丧尸走出去了吧
Say, maybe he turned into a zombie and walked out
丧尸来了
It's the zombie
你们
You guys
吃我这招  你个丧尸
Take that, you zombie
接下来交给我
I'll take it from here
丧尸去死
Die, zombie
干得漂亮  南希警官
Good police work, Officer Nancy
这位不是丧尸
This guy's not a zombie
只是一普普通通的卫生检查员
He's just an ordinary health inspector
对
Yes
我要冒着再次被打的危险
And at the risk of being hit again
给你们这个东西
I'd like to present you with this
蟹堡王
合格
蟹老板快看
Mr. Krabs, look
我们检查合格了
We passed the inspection
万岁
Hooray
大家都快来
Come on, everybody
蟹黄堡五折优惠
Krabby Patties at half price
其实没这回事
Well, not really
老天爷啊  我要来份蟹黄堡
Oh, boy, I'd like a Krabby Patty
故事到此为止了
Well, that's the story
对  他们应该都是白痴吧
Yes, they are all idiots, aren't they?
白痴盒子
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
看见什么东西了吗  派大星
See anything yet, Patrick?
我得要戴眼镜
I need my glasses
是邮车
It's the mail truck
包裹来了
Our package
我都不知道今天是快乐跳跳傻子节
I didn't realize it was Happy Hopping Moron Day
海绵宝宝吗
SpongeBob SquarePants?
就是我
That's me
好大的盒子
That's a big box
谢谢了
Thank you
海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
什么时候可以不跳了
When do we stop hopping?
再等三十秒  派大星
Thirty more seconds, Patrick
他们怕是订了一辈子用不完的泡泡皂
They probably ordered
a lifetime supply of bubble soap
新款电视
A brand-new television?
小心
Easy
本来我还以为他们傻到不能再傻了
Just when I thought they couldn't get any stupider
我把事情弄清楚
Let me get this straight
你们两个订了台大屏幕电视
you two ordered a giant screen television
就只是为了玩这个盒子吗
just so you could play in the box?
很聪明吧
Pretty smart, huh?
我本来以为没法用
I thought it wouldn't work
还真不走寻常路
That's quite a plan there
可是等下
But wait
我还有事情要问你们两个
There was something else I wanted to ask you two
是那什么来着
Now, what was it?
对了对了
Yeah, yeah
你们两个是不是没脑子
Don't you two have any brains?
章鱼哥  我们不需要电视
Squidward, we don't need television
只需要有
Not as long as we have our
想象力
imagination
我还真没这么想过呢
I never thought of it that way
真是妙啊
That's really something
能拿你们电视走吗
Can I have your TV?
只要有
With
想象力
imagination
想当什么就当什么
I can be anything I want
当海盗
A pirate
当橄榄球球员
A football player
当海星
A starfish
派大星  你本来就已经是海星了
Patrick, you're already a starfish
看见没  章鱼哥
See, Squidward?
想象力有用
It works
你来试试看
You try
那好  我来想象
Okay, let's see
我想象我在看电视
I'm imaging myself watching TV
电视就出现在那了
and there it is
我能拿吗  海绵宝宝
Can I have it, SpongeBob?
能啊  章鱼哥
Sure, Squidward
好啊  好啊
Oh, boy, oh, boy
那行吧  章鱼哥
Okay, Squidward
要是改主意  我们就待这盒子里等你
But if you change your mind, we'll be in this box
来玩爬山大冒险吧
Let's play Mountain Climbing Adventure
那就出发
Let's go for it
手套
Gloves
有了
Check
帽子
Hats
有了
Check
内裤
Underwear
有了
Check
好了派大星
Okay, Patrick
爬上去系好安全绳
Climb up there and secure this rope
没问题
You got it
派大星
Patrick
派大星  你爬得太高了
Patrick, you're going too high
希望他们给盒子开了通气口
I hope they put some air holes in that box
放轻松  派大星
Take it easy, Patrick
你得适应环境
You've got to acclimate
等我死了再放轻松
I'll take it easy when I'm dead
我在跟海神王握手
I'm shaking hands with Neptune
精益求精
Excelsior
遥控器哪去了
Where's that remote?
我就是蜥蜴王
I am the lizard king
派大星
Patrick?
Patrick
应该要把声音放小点
I think we should keep our voices down
不然可能会引发雪崩的
We might start an avalanche
说什么
What?
我说
I said
应该要把声音放小点
I think we should keep our voices down
防止出雪崩
in case of avalanches
把什么放小点
What should we keep down?
白痴
Morons
说话的声音
Our voices
能不能给我闭嘴
Will you two shut up?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
快抓紧我
Hold me
撑住  兄弟
Hang in there, buddy
救援直升机马上就到
The chopper's on the way
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
我腿给冻僵了
My legs are frozen solid
你得拿锯子把我腿给锯掉
You'll have to cut them off with a saw
不行  派大星
No, Patrick
我做不到
I can't do that
为什么
Why not?
因为我已经把我胳膊给割掉了
Because I already cut off my own arms
不要
No
怎么
What the?
你们两个咋发出来声音的
How were you two making that noise?
什么声音  章鱼哥
What noise, Squidward?
我就只能听到我们发出来的笑声
I could only hear the sound of our laughter
是没错
Yes
可是那些音效
But those sound effects
有雪崩  跟跟跟
the avalanche, the, the, the
第二场雪崩别忘了
Don't forget the second avalanche
算了吧
Forget it
不知道我干嘛要待外面浪费时间
I don't know why I'm wasting my time out here
本来这个时候我还可以看新款电视的
when I could be watching my brand new television
登山者们请注意
Attention, climbers
坚持住
Please hold on
锯子马上就到
The saws are on the way
你们是怎么做到的
How are you doing that?
先在海拔15000英尺的地方建大本营
First we establish a base camp at 15,000 feet
我说的是声音
The noises
你们两个怎么发出的那些声音
How are you two making those noises?
简单
That's easy
只要来个盒子
All you need is a box
还有
And
想象力
imagination
你们是不是要说我没有想象力
Are you trying to say that I have no imagination?
我随便一根触手里掌握的想象力
I have more imagination in one tentacle
都比你们两个全身加起来的还多
than you two have in your whole bodies
那就好
That's good
你就只要有个盒子就行了
Now all you need is a box
倒要给他们见识
I'll show them
里面肯定有盒子
There's got to be one in here
这个帽子盒应该不错
This hat box should do nicely
我怎么从来没戴过这帽子
Why haven't I worn this yet?
请注意
Attention
你已经被包围了
We have you surrounded
举起双手马上出来
Come out with your hands up
他们找我干嘛
What do they want with me?
我又做什么了
What did I do?
很明显我违反了新出的某种踢盒子法了
Obviously I violated some new box-kicking law
警官  你们看
Look, officers
一切都没事
Everything's okay
下次不犯了
I won't do it again
你们不可能会活捉我的  警察
You'll never take me alive, coppers
不行  约翰尼
No, Johnny
不要这样做
Don't do it
又有盒子了
Another box
我得好好放松
I got to try to relax
电视声应该能盖过他们的幼稚游戏声
Perhaps I can drown out
their childish games with a little TV
组装盒子的最后阶段就在此处完成
It is here that the boxes
reach their final stage of assembly
下面这个盒子证明了这个方程
The equation is demonstrated here by this box
我今年买不起礼物
I couldn't afford a present this year
所以我给你送了这个盒子
so I got you this box
我也送的这个
That's what I got you
就没一个跟盒子没关系的节目吗
Isn't there anything on that isn't about boxes?
欢迎回到拳击锦标赛
And welcome back to Championship Boxing
盒 子
这节目倒还好
I guess this is okay
至少说跟盒子没多大关系
I mean, it's not really about boxes
我服了
I give up
三
Three
二
Two
一
One
发射
Blast off
他们是怎么做到的
How are they doing that?
这可是我听过最真实的火箭发射声了
That was the most realistic space launch I ever heard
一定有什么能解释这现象
There must be an explanation
章鱼哥  快想啊你
Think, Squidward, think
章鱼哥好笨
Squidward's such a jerk
嘲笑我是吧
Laugh at me, will they?
好了  在哪
All right, where is it?
我在这
Here I am
什么在哪  章鱼哥
Where's what, Squidward?
别拿同样的话回我
Don't "Where's what, Squidward?" me
录音机在哪
Where's the tape recorder?
没有录音机  章鱼哥
We don't have a tape recorder, Squidward
别拿同样的话回我
Don't "We don't have a tape recorder, Squidward" me
可我们真没有
But we don't
倒是有个录音机盒
We have a tape recorder box
那好
All right
你们两个让开  我要进来了
Make way, you two, I'm coming in
欢迎登船  章鱼哥
Welcome aboard, Squidward
你登上的这艘船名叫
You've just set sail on the S.S.
想象力号
Imagination
我们唯一的目的地就是奇幻冒险
where our only destination is fantastic adventure
你要先去哪
Where do you want to go first?
不去
No, no
用不着管我
Don't mind me
我就待这光看着
I'm just here to observe
可是章鱼哥  你不懂吗
But Squidward, don't you see?
待这光看着
Waiting and watching?
这可不符合盒子的内在精神
That's not what the box is about
内在精神在于
It's about
想象力
imagination
那好那好
All right, fine
带我去机器海盗岛
Take me to Robot Pirate Island
我要跟月球上的牛仔掰手腕
I wanna arm-wrestle with cowboys on the moon
赶紧摔  这样我好回去看电视
Just do it so I can get back and watch TV
好了  章鱼哥
Okay, Squidward
机器海盗岛到了
Robot Pirate Island it is
同伴好
Ahoy matey
你们犯了错  得走甲板落海去
For that you'll walk the plank
这玩意怎么就不打开了
Why won't this thing turn on?
那好那好
All right, fine
你们不给我看的话
If you don't want to show me
我也就不管了
I don't care
我还有更好的事要做
I've got better things to do
才不会走来走去想你们怎么操作的
than pace the floor
wondering how you two work this thing
那两个怎么操作的
How do those two work that thing?
肯定有什么秘密按钮开关之类的东西
There's got to be a secret button
or a switch or something
听人家的声音
I mean, listen to that
一听就是机器海盗岛
Now, that sounds like Robot Pirate Island
章鱼哥  快想啊你
Think, Squidward, think
有了
I got it
等到那两个上床睡觉了
When those two go to bed
我就偷偷溜进去找按钮
I'll sneak in there and find that button
等个一整晚我都愿意
I'll wait all night if I have to
我得睡一觉  给我的想象力加个油
I need sleep to refuel my imagination tanks
还是不敢相信海盗把机器人都打败了
I still can't believe
those pirates beat all those robots
明早再见了
Yeah, see you in the morning
晚安  派大星
Good night, Patrick
这什么东西
Hello, what's this?
谨以此牌匾纪念勇猛海盗们
This plaque is to commemorate the brave pirates
为安全护送该盒子
who gave their lives to keep this box
免受机器人威胁而牺牲的壮举
safe from the Robot Menace
永远铭记
Lest we forget
我得赶紧找按钮
I've got to find that button quick
肯定就在这边哪个地方的
It's got to be around here somewhere
什么都没看到
I don't see anything
就一空盒子而已
It's just an empty box
可能还真是他们的想象力弄出来的
Maybe it really was their imagination
冷静  章鱼哥
Get it together, Squidward
你刚在说什么
What are you saying?
我难道真的会相信
I mean, do I really believe that
要是我坐这假装在开赛车
if I sit here and pretend to drive a race car
然后我就突然会听到声音了
that I'm suddenly going to start hearing noises?
怎么
What the?
还真的有用
It actually works
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
好耶
Oh, boy
比电视强太多了
This beats TV by a long shot
垃圾
这是我玩得最开心的一次了
This is the most fun I've ever had
小蜗快听
Listen to that, Gary
章鱼哥可终于会用盒子了
Squidward finally made the box work after all
太棒了
That's so great
垃圾场
就差两圈就要到终点了
Only two more laps to the finish line
我领先
I'm in the lead
快让道
Out of my way
就快到了
I'm almost there
胜利属于我
Victory is mine
我们盒子不见了
Our box is gone
可惜啊
Oh, well
有了  去看看章鱼哥吧
I know, let's go see Squidward
希望他今天不会太沮丧了
I hope he's not too down in the dumps today
在 垃 圾 场